Rohit K. Shinde

Personal Info

Address

C1-301, Dreams Estate, Hadapsar Pune, MH, 411028

Phone

827 526 6989

E-mail

rokshinde@gmail.com

Skills

- UI Design
- Web Design
- Graphic design
- Logo design
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Website graphics
- Production layouts
- Illustration
- Branding strategies
- Image manipulation

Tech. Skills

- PHOTOSHOP
- ILLUSTRATOR
- INDESIGN
- HTML/CSS

Design Skills

- SOCIAL MEDIA DESIGN
- PRINT DESIGN
- TYPOGRAPHY
- LAYOUT
- COLOR THEORY

Soft SKills

- Creativity
- Planning
- Leadership
- Time Management
- Communication
- Problem Solving

Experienced Graphic Artist and Designer bringing 2+ years' experience applying technical and creative abilities to diverse customer projects. Highly effective at collaborating with artistic, project, production and administrative leadership to complete tasks according to budget and schedule goals.

Work History

2018-09 -Current

Web And Graphic Designer

Indian Magic Eye Pvt. Ltd., Pune, MH
Currently working as Graphic & Web designer in the digital space.

Industry skills explored in this company:

- Logo designing and building online brand
- Concept building for online marketing and Social media
- Innovative minimalistic & trending designs
- Campaign designing

2018-03 -2018-08

Production Mentor

Global Advertisement Solutions Private Limited, Pune, MH

Handled a team size of 30 + Designers after my appraisal.

My key roles were:

- 1) Asset mapping of the team in terms of graphics
- 2) Concept building and developing design strategies
- 3) Follow up for tight deadlines
- 4) Getting the work done in tight deadlines with matching quality standards.
- 5) Client co-ordination and output management

2016-07 -2018-02

Graphic Designer

Global Advertisement Solutions Private Limited, Pune, MH

I started my career as a designer with 3 months training and was a Production Associate in the company.

Industry skills explored in this company:

- Logo designing and building the brand
- Concept building for offline marketing collateral which includes Brochures, Print banner, Letterheads, leaflets etc.
- -Conceptualized and developed graphics products for Print Media, Small Medium sized businesses and worldwide clients using Photoshop and Illustrator.

Education

Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Engineering

JSPM's Jaywantrao Sawant College of Engineering, , Pune

2012

High School Diploma

BSD Polytechnic, Dhule